(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins
G-A-M-E-R-S
Holo!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Holo!
ころね！
Korone!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Holo!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Holo!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the show starts
Fubuki!
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Okayu!
Korone!
Are you ready?
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Okayu!
Fubuki!
Korone!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin shortly. Please wait for a while.
G A M E R S Fubuki!
G A M E R S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
I'm ready? Mio!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G A M E R S おかゆ！
G A M E R S Okayu!
G A M E R S フブキ！
G A M E R S Fubuki!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ミオ！
Mio!
hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ
hololive GAMERS fes. Super Super Super Super Gamers
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the show starts
公演ハッシュタグ #超ゲマズ2_day1
Concert Hashtag: #ChoGamerz2_day1
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
I'm ready?
How?
がおー！
Gao!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ミオ！
Mio!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
く...
Ku...
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
く...
Ku...
みお！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ
開演までしばらくお待ちください
hololive GAMERS fes. Super Super Super Super Gamers
Please wait a while until the show begins.
READY GO!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
フブキもやるぞ！
Fubuki is going to do it too!
ミオも嬉しいよ！
Mio is happy too!
WE ARE GAMERS!
みんな待ってた？
Have you all been waiting?
いっぱい楽しんでってね！
Have lots of fun, okay!
WE ARE GAMERS!
フブニャ！
Fubunya!
こんこん狐だ御上々
Kon-kon kitsune da gojoujou
白上でも耳白上フブキです
I'm Shirokami Fubuki, white even with my ears
突っ込んでちゃ始まらない
It won't start if you keep retorting
君もつかまみニュボしなさい
You should also try Nyubo-ing
ハイ！プレイ！
High! Play!
イェー！
Yeah!
ハイ！プレイ！
High! Play!
イェー！
Yeah!
ぽんぽんと絶好調
Pon-pon and in top form
AIじゃないしたぷゆはMC
I'm not AI, and Shita-puyu is the MC
赤い空より金星が欲しい
I want Venus more than the red sky
ミオしゃ！
Miosha!
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ
It's me, it's me, it's Ookami Mio
黒上でも耳大神ミオ
Ookami Mio, black even with my ears
突っ込んで捏ねます雷様
Retorting and kneading, the Thunder God
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop
つまりスはポト女
In short, S is a Poto-woman
壊しせっせチャオーオホー
Breaking and working, Ciao-oho-
タロット占いで見る未来
The future seen through Tarot reading
ほらゲームやりたくない？
Hey, don't you want to play a game?
四人そろえばまず最強
If the four of us gather, we're the strongest
君も遊ぼうよBダッシュして
You should play too, B-dashing along
もぐもぐして
Munching and crunching
ベルあげちゃうわ
I'll give you a bell
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃおう
Let's capture your heart too
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
初見も五感も大丈夫よ
First time or using five senses, it's okay
ゲームは楽しいね
Games are fun, aren't they?
G-A-M-E-R
WE ARE GAMERS!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
いつももぐもぐ猫又おかゆ
Always munching, Nekomata Okayu
おにぎりおにぎりはいどうぞ
Rice ball, rice ball, here you go
キラキラフラフラしょうがない
Sparkling and wandering, it can't be helped
猫だもん　もうそこ僕でよくない？
I'm a cat, isn't it fine if I stay there?
まったりゆっくり奏でるリズム
A rhythm played out chill and slow
前方停止するここはいつも
Stopping ahead, this is always the place
前方降臨オッケー
Descent ahead is OK
毎日僕と一緒さ
You're with me every day
ころね！
Korone!
おはよー指指わーわー
Good morning, fingers, fingers, wow wow
パンをこねこね戌神ころね
Kneading the bread, Inugami Korone
検索あまり夜勤チャゴース
Searching too much, night shift Chagousu
スーパー寝るな直げど朝コケ
Super don't sleep, direct but morning collapse
なまろイントネーション割れるリアクション
Raw intonation, cracking reaction
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信者
First, will you offer your fingers? Broadcaster
わかったなほねしちオッケー
Got it, Honeshichi OK
小宇宙のレトロゲーお届け
Delivering retro games from the cosmos
四人そろえばまず最強
If the four of us gather, we're the strongest
フラグ立てれば復活心
Set a flag and revive your spirit
目の鍛えて
Train your eyes
狙い打ち
And take your aim
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃおう
Let's restore your heart too
ワクワクするねこの感情
This feeling is so exciting
第9天うかやめれないだって
I can't stop, because it's the 9th heaven
ゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I love games!
突然ですが...ボーナスチャレンジのお時間です！
This is sudden, but... it's time for the Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスをして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Let's aim for a high score by responding in a loud voice!
Are you ready?
コンコン！
Kon-kon!
ミオミオ！
Mio-mio!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu-mogu!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi-yubi!
コンコン！
Kon-kon!
ミオミオ！
Mio-mio!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu-mogu!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi-yubi!
PERFECT!
四人そろえばまず最強
If the four of us gather, we're the strongest
上手くいかなくてもノーコンする
Even if it doesn't go well, no continues
リフレッシュして
Refresh yourself
あきらめない
And don't give up
エンディングを
Let's go and see
見に行こう
The ending together
君のハートも攻略しちゃおう
Let's capture your heart too
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
初見も五感も大丈夫よ
First time or using five senses, it's okay
ようこそゲームは楽しいね
Welcome, games are fun, aren't they?
G-A-M-E-R
WE ARE GAMERS!
こうしてさいたまスーパーアリーナに平和が訪れたのであった。
And so, peace returned to Saitama Super Arena.
はい、ということで始まりましたー！
Alright, and so it begins!
ホロライブゲーマーズです、超超超超ゲーマーズ2です！
We are hololive GAMERS! This is Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2!
はい、じゃあちょっとね、自己紹介やっていきますかね。
Okay, let's go ahead and do some introductions.
はい、皆様、こんこんきつね！
Alright everyone, Kon-kon-kitsune!
こんこんきつねー！
Kon-kon-kitsune!
はい、白上フブキです、よろしくお願いします。
I'm Shirakami Fubuki, nice to meet you!
そして、そしてね、まあ1曲目ちょっとね、あの We Are Gamers やらせてもらったんですけども...
And also, we just performed "We Are Gamers" as our first song...
もうついにね、4人ということで、いるじゃないですか赤いのが、さあ！
And now that all four of us are finally here, we have the one in red! Come on!
はい！
Yes!
おおおーい！うちうち、うちだよ！
Heyyy! It's me, me, it's me!
大神ミオです、お待たせいたしましたー！
I'm Ookami Mio, sorry to keep you waiting!
あ、お待たせしました、大神ミオの皆様いらっしゃいませ。
Oh, thanks for waiting. Welcome, everyone, to Ookami Mio.
はい、続いて！
Okay, next!
はい！もぐもぐー？
Yes! Mogu-mogu...?
おかゆーん！
Okayu-n!
はい、どうも、猫又おかゆです。
Hi there, I'm Nekomata Okayu.
今日はね、最高の思い出を作って、楽しんじゃいましょう。
Let's make some amazing memories and have a great time today.
はい、そして！
Okay, and!
はい、ゆー？
Yes, Yu...?
びびびー！
Bi-bi-bi!
戌神ころねです！
I'm Inugami Korone!
みんな今日は大事な日なの、何の日か知ってる？
Everyone, today is an important day. Do you know what day it is?
今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日！おめでとう！
Today is Shohei Ohtani's birthday! Congratulations!
ということで、戌神ころねですよろしくお願いします。
Anyway, I'm Inugami Korone. Nice to meet you!
ということでね、改めまして4人揃って、せーの！
And so, now that all four of us are here together... one, two!
ホロライブゲーマーズフェス、超超超超ゲーマーズ2！
hololive GAMERS fes. Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2!
その DAY1 がここ、さいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕でございます！
Day 1 is now officially starting here at Saitama Super Arena!
なんとですね、あの DAY1, DAY2、用意席とか完売ということで。
Believe it or not, all the available seats for Day 1 and Day 2 are sold out.
DAY1, DAY2 ともに約1万5, 6, 7千とかのファンの皆様が今日来てくださってる。
About 15,000 to 17,000 fans have come to see us for both Day 1 and Day 2.
すごーい！
That's amazing!
運営さんから DAY1, DAY2 合わせて3.5万人ぐらいですって。
The staff told me that there are about 35,000 people here over the two days.
すごすぎるー！
That's incredible!
すごいね。ほぼ人間じゃん。
Wow. That's almost a city's worth of people.
ほぼ人間だよ！人間以外いないだろ、ここ。
Of course they are! There's no one but humans here.
昨年は国立代々木競技場だったんですけども、今回はさいたまスーパーアリーナということで。
Last year it was at the Yoyogi National Stadium, but this time we're at Saitama Super Arena.
すごいですよもう、ありがとうございます。
It's really something else. Thank you so much.
このイベントはですね、ゲームが大好きな我々ゲーマーズを中心に...
This event centers around us Gamers, who love video games...
超超超超ゲーマーズ2とは...
What is Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2...?
超豪華なゲストと一緒に、様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり...
Where we'll be tackling various game titles with super-luxurious guests...
ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントです！
And delivering live performances in this premium event!
突然出てきて「3Dなの？」って感じなんですけど、4人のお揃いの衣装、お披露目でございます！
We just popped up, and you might be thinking "Wait, they're in 3D?", but we're debuting our matching costumes!
かわいいー！
They're so cute!
本当この衣装かわいいから着たいねーって言ってたら、用意してくださいました。
We were saying how cute these costumes are and how much we wanted to wear them, and they made them for us.
夢のようだよねー。
It's like a dream come true.
さらに、会場では一部撮影OKなパートがありますので...
Furthermore, there are parts of the event where photography is permitted in the venue...
そちらではですね、スマホでお写真を撮っていただけると嬉しいです。
So we'd love it if you could take some photos with your smartphones during those times.
ぜひ最後まで一緒に楽しみましょう！
Let's all have fun together until the very end!
ということで、1人ずつちょっと意気込みお願いしたいと思います。
So, I'd like to ask each of you to share your aspirations for today.
じゃあまずは、ミオから！
Okay, let's start with Mio!
はい！えー今年は、去年はね、ちょっとお休みしちゃったんですけど...
Okay! Well, this year... Since I had to take a break last year...
んですけど、今年は4人でね、
...but since the four of us
無事に開催することができたので、
were able to safely hold this together this year,
明日も無事に終えられるように、
so that we can finish tomorrow safely as well,
体調管理だけはしっかりして、
I'll take good care of my health,
2日間過ごしたいと思いまーす！
and I want to spend these two days together!
頑張るぞー！
I'll do my best!
ではでは、
Well then,
続いては、
next up is
おかゆ！
Okayu!
まぁ僕はね、去年に引き続きの参加となるんですが、
Well, I'm participating again after last year,
まぁ今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日ということで！
well, today is Shohei Ohtani's birthday!
大谷関係ないやろ！
Ohtani has nothing to do with this!
すごい人だけどさ、
He's an amazing person, but...
ギャグ打率3割！
a Gag Batting Average of .300!
目指して頑張りたいと思います！
I'll do my best to aim for that!
ちょっと当ててください。
Please cheer for me a bit.
おかゆならもっといけそうだけどな。
Okayu seems like she could go higher though.
そして！
And!
今日はね、翔平に素敵なプレゼントを、
Today, so that I can deliver a wonderful gift...
届けられるように、
to Shohei,
こーはなりよー！
Ko-ha-na-ri-yo!
せめて「ころスキ」に届けてくれ。
At least deliver it to "Koro-Suki".
あ、ころスキに届けます！
Ah, I'll deliver it to Koro-Suki!
そしてそして！
And and!
白上はですね、皆さま、昨年に引き続きまして、
As for me, everyone, continuing from last year,
なんとあの台本の8割を白上が読み上げるということで！
Shirakami will be reading about 80% of the script!
全力で、喉をいたわりつつ、
I'll take care of my throat with all my might,
台本は白上だらけな。
the script is full of Shirakami.
なので喉が枯れ始めたら、「あ、頑張ってるな」と思って、
so if my voice starts getting hoarse, please think "Ah, she's working hard",
いっぱいペンライト振ってください！
and wave your light sticks a lot!
お前らの声に負けねーから、よろしく！
I won't lose to your voices, so look forward to it!
そしてですね、今日と明日行われる「超超超超ゲーマーズ2」は、
Also, "Chou Chou Chou Chou Gamers 2" held today and tomorrow
ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！
is being live-streamed on ABEMA PPV!
見てるー？
Are you watching?
見てらー？
コメントも我々見えておりますよ。
We can see your comments as well.
ねえ、ありがとうございます。
Yes, thank you very much.
こちら配信チケットは絶賛発売中です。
Streaming tickets are now on sale.
イベントが終わっても、8月4日月曜日の23時59分まで、
Even after the event, until 23:59 on Monday, August 4th,
何度でも見返すことができまーす！
you can watch it as many times as you like!
購入特典としましては、Day 1とDay 2で異なるシチュエーションの、
As a purchase bonus, for Day 1 and Day 2, there are different situations of
限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます。
limited original voice dramas included.
Day 1は「秘密の事前プロデュースボイス」。
Day 1 is "Secret Advance Produce Voice".
これエッチなやつかな？
Is this an ecchi one?
違います。
No.
そしてDay 2は、「内緒の超ヒマズお疲れ様ボイス」。
And Day 2 is "Secret Super After-Gamer-Otsukare Voice".
これエッチなやつかな？
Is this an ecchi one?
やめな！
Stop it!
こちらの2つボイス、エッチじゃないです。聴いてください。
These two voices are not ecchi. Please listen to them.
あとはですね、我々の直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像も、
Also, live photos with our handwritten messages
ついてきますので、ぜひチェックしてください！
will be included, so please check it out!
さらに！昨年行われました「超超超超ゲーマーズ」の、
Furthermore! The "Chou Chou Chou Chou Gamers" held last year,
ダイジェストがABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
the digest is now available on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のもね、めちゃめちゃ面白かったのでぜひとも見てください。
Last year's was also very interesting, so please take a look.
さらにさらに！イベント後にグッズの受注販売が開始します！
Furthermore! Goods pre-orders will start after the event!
ありがたいことにDay 1のグッズがなんか完売らしくて、
Gratefully, it seems the Day 1 goods are sold out,
皆さんありがとうございます！
thank you everyone!
こちらグッズの受注販売の期間が、本日の朝10時から、
The pre-order period for these goods is from 10:00 this morning,
7月21日の23時59分まで、
until 23:59 on July 21st,
Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中でございます。
available at the Cyber Goods Store.
こちらのグッズ、9月下旬までにはお届け予定とのことです。
These goods are scheduled to be delivered by late September.
そしてなんと！事後限定グッズとしまして、
And wow! As post-event limited goods,
アクリルパネルが追加されます！
an acrylic panel will be added!
イベント限定グッズが手に入る最後のチャンスなので、
This is your last chance to get event-limited goods,
ぜひぜひこちらチェックしてください！
so please definitely check it out!
今の話を、大人しく聞けない生徒みたいになってます。
They've become like students who won't listen quietly.
はい、先生話すからねー。
Yes, Teacher is talking now.
さらにさらに！もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが、
Furthermore! I think some of you may already know,
NTTドコモさんの「home 5G」とのコラボが実施いたしましたー！
a collaboration with NTT Docomo's "home 5G" has been implemented!
先生の話は聞かなくてもいいけど、声は出さないで！
You don't have to listen to Teacher, but don't make any noise!
すみませんでしたー。
We are sorry.
今、NTTドコモさんのご紹介してたでしょう？
I was just introducing NTT Docomo, wasn't I?
友達！
Friends!
友達か！
Are we friends?!
では、どうぞ！
Well, go ahead!
あ、入口でもらえるうちわ、皆さんゲットしましたか？
Oh, did everyone get the fan they give out at the entrance?
もらった方ー？
Who got one?
もらったうちわも使って、熱中症対策万全にして...
Use the fan you got to take full precautions against heatstroke...
...最後まで楽しんでください！
...and please enjoy until the end!
まだまだ続きますよ！
It's still going!
超ゲマズ、我らゲマズを応援したいっていう声が多かったので...
Since there were many voices saying they want to support us Gamers at Chou Gemazu...
...今回イベントでチアスポットさんとのコラボをすることになりました！
...we've decided to collaborate with CheerSPOT for this event!
イエーイ！
Yay!
誰でも簡単に、好きなアーティストの場所に白上たちゲマズの応援広告を出すことができます！
Anyone can easily put up support advertisements for us Gamers, including Shirakami, at their favorite artist's location!
これすごい！
This is amazing!
会場内もね、これあの、なんと！ね、スポットが我らになってまして、びっくりしました。
Inside the venue too, what! The spots have become us, I was surprised.
そうなんだ。
Is that so.
見てないの！？
You haven't seen them!?
見てたよ！見てたよ、あのパネルのやつか。
I saw them! I saw them, you mean those panels.
そうそう。見に来てない方は会場内に確かあったと思いますので、よかったら見てください。
Right, right. I think they were in the venue for those who haven't seen them yet, so please check them out.
はい、そしてさらに、さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初披露！
Yes, and furthermore, in the Saitama Super Arena venue, for the first time we're revealing life-sized figures!
3月のEXPO会場で発表されましたフブミオ等身大に続きまして、おかころフィギュアも発売予定となっております！
Following the FubuMio life-sized figures announced at the EXPO in March, OkaKoro figures are also scheduled to be released!
イエーイ！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
やったー！事前の告知配信ではさ、なかったらおかゆん毛玉なんじゃないかって言ったんですけど、ちゃんと揃ってました！
Yay! In the pre-announcement stream, I said if they weren't there, Okayun would just be a hairball, but they're all here!
揃ってましたね！めちゃめちゃ可愛かったです。ありがとうございます。
They're all here! They were so cute. Thank you.
そしてまた、本日から新作のフィギュアがデザインココから受注開始です！
And also, from today, new figures from Design Coco are open for pre-orders!
イエーイ！可愛い！
Yay! Cute!
イベント開催を記念して、8月7日までにココストアで予約してくれた方には、特典のステッカーをプレゼントされるそうです。
To commemorate the event, those who pre-order at Coco Store by August 7th will receive a bonus sticker.
可愛すぎる。
Too cute.
やっぱり白上とミオも欲しいなーと思った、そこのあなた！あなた！あなたー！
For you there who thought "I want Shirakami and Mio too!" You! You! You!
なんと超ゲマズ2の開催を記念して、期間限定でフブミオ追加予約を開始じゃー！
What, to commemorate the holding of Chou Gemazu 2, we're starting additional pre-orders for FubuMio for a limited time!
やったー！
Yay!
逃したよっていうのもね、あの、何個かエゴサで見かけましたので、これを機にぜひともご予約お願いします！
I saw several comments on Ego Search saying "I missed it," so please take this opportunity to pre-order!
そして最後に、カンブル様による協賛企業グッズ...
And finally, we have the introduction of the sponsored company goods by Canble...
...超超超超ポップコーンと超超超超グリルチキンのご紹介でございます！
...the Chou Chou Chou Chou Popcorn and Chou Chou Chou Chou Grilled Chicken!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが前面に出たデザインとなってるとのことです。
It's said that the design features the key visual of this event prominently.
ポップコーンは税込み1000円で、缶詰めは税込み1500円での販売でございます。
Popcorn is 1000 yen including tax, and the canned food is sold for 1500 yen including tax.
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、缶詰めはグリルチキン味になってます。
The popcorn is salted caramel flavor, and the canned food is grilled chicken flavor.
トレカもついてる！
It even comes with a trading card!
こちらのグッズは他のグッズと異なり、受注生産ではなく、数量限定商品のため...
Unlike other goods, these are not made-to-order but are limited quantity items, so...
...お早めにゲットしてください！
...please get them early!
集合アクリルパネルも含めて、事後でしか購入できないグッズですので、皆さんぜひチェックしてください。
Including the collective acrylic panel, these are goods that can only be purchased after the fact, so everyone please check them out.
なんと、ちなみに今回は韓国でライブビューイングもやってるそうですよ。韓国の皆様、アンニョンハセヨ！
What, by the way, it seems they are also doing a live viewing in Korea this time. Everyone in Korea, Annyeonghaseyo!
アンニョンハセヨ！
Annyeonghaseyo!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
ではですね、色々ご紹介も終わりましたので、早速最初に行うゲームタイトルを発表しちゃいましょう！
Well then, now that we've finished various introductions, let's announce the title of the first game we'll play right away!
行きますよ、せーの！
Here we go, one, two!
こちら！
This!
ビビッター！
Bibittar!
こちらルールは超簡単。
The rules for this are super simple.
ミニゲームに対し、タイミングよくボタンを押して、ギリギリで止めるだけ。
For the mini-game, just press the button with good timing and stop at the very last second.
はい、我らのですね、度胸を試す究極のビビリチェッカーゲームとなっております。
Yes, it's the ultimate chicken checker game to test our courage.
よりギリギリを攻めると、クールの評価がもらえるそうです。
It seems if you push it even closer to the limit, you get a "Cool" rating.
今回ですね、我ら個人戦でございます。
This time, it's an individual battle for us.
一つのミニゲームに対し、二人がそれぞれ挑戦します。
Two people will challenge each mini-game.
様々な組み合わせで合計6ゲーム、行わせていただきたいと思います。
We'd like to play a total of 6 games in various combinations.
こちらですね、我らのクールの合計数で1位を決めたいと思いますので、よろしくお願いします。
We'll decide the winner based on our total number of "Cool" ratings, so please look forward to it.
ではですね、ゲームを始める前に、なんと今回ですね、巨大コントローラーを用意してくれたということで...
Well then, before starting the game, what, this time they've prepared a giant controller for us...
はい、召喚しましょう。これでちょっと会場の皆さんも一緒に...
Yes, let's summon it. With this, everyone in the venue together...
「出でよ、巨大コントローラー！」って叫んでくれると嬉しいです。できますか！？
"Come forth, giant controller!" I'd be happy if you'd shout that. Can you do it!?
いであれ！巨大コントローラー！
Come forth! Giant controller!
じゃあ、どの順番でチャレンジしていきますか？
Well then, in what order should we take on the challenge?
我こそはというの…
Anyone who thinks they're the one...
じゃあでも、ミオしゃじゃない？やっぱり。
But wait, shouldn't it be Miosha after all?
ミオしゃ おかえりー！
Welcome back, Miosha!
やったほうがいいって！
You definitely should do it!
じゃあ、続いてはどうする？
Okay, who's next?
２番目やりたい！やりたい、やりたい！
I want to be second! I want to, I want to!
じゃあ、おかゆ２番目？
So, Okayu second?
じゃあ おかゆ２番目。
Okay, Okayu second.
じゃあ、ころねはどうする？
Then, what about Korone?
３番目はどうしようかね。
What should I do for third?
いや、トリは嫌だ。３番手。
No, I don't want to be last. I'll go third.
じゃあ、順番としましては、一番最初はミオおかゆの対戦になります。
Okay, for the order, the first match will be Mio and Okayu.
ということでじゃあ、ミオがやっていきましょう！
With that, let's have Mio give it a go!
ミオしゃんさ、僕が勝っても泣かないでね。
Miosha, don't cry even if I win, okay?
おかゆには何度も負かされてきてるし。
I've been beaten by Okayu many times before.
この猫めちゃくちゃミニゲーム系強いんですよ。
This cat is incredibly strong at mini-games.
そうだね、ちょっと強いよね。
True, I am a bit strong.
このゲームは初見だからさ！
But this game is a first for us!
そうだよ、初めてやるよ。
That's right, it's our first time playing it.
適性が高すぎるんだって、ミニゲームの。
Your aptitude for mini-games is just way too high.
確かに、それはあるかも。
True, that might be it.
だからね、なるべくでもそこでうちが勝ったらめっちゃ奇跡的ってことでしょ！
So, if I can win here, it would be a total miracle!
奇跡起こっちゃうかも！
A miracle might just happen!
それじゃあやっていきますか！まずは「試練の２」というものを…
Well then, shall we start? First up is 'The Ordeal 2'...
やっていこうかなと思います。
Let's see how this goes.
これスタッフさんがやったんですが、スタッフさんが強すぎる。
The staff tried this, and they were way too strong.
じゃあ、準備いいですか、ミオ？
Alright, are you ready, Mio?
はい！頑張りミオ！
Yes! I'll do my best!
応援しててね！スタート！
Please cheer for me! Start!
あちらのお客様からグラスを滑らせろ。
Slide the glass to that customer over there.
マスター、あちらの美しい女性にこれと同じものを。
Master, give that beautiful woman over there the same as this.
かしこまりました。なんだこいつの顔！
Understood. Look at this guy's face!
じゃあクリックすると…まず練習ね。
When you click... First is practice.
グラスを滑らせろ！
Slide the glass!
左にゲージがある。どうやら長押ししてゲージを貯めるらしい。
There's a gauge on the left. It seems you fill it by long-pressing.
ことか？おっ！もう？おおーっ！
Like this? Oh! Already? Whoa!
そこならGoodですね、マスター。
That would be 'Good', Master.
ゴールするとかじゃなきゃいけないんでしょ？
I have to reach the goal, right?
じゃあ、本番いきます！
Okay, time for the real thing!
すごーい！やった！セーフ！
Amazing! I did it! Safe!
すごいすごいすごい！
Incredible, incredible, incredible!
何そのポーズ！すごい！
What's with that pose! Awesome!
真ん中でやりたいんですが！
I wanted to stop it right in the middle!
ミオが今５０だったかな？
Was Mio's score just 50?
５０です。０.５０ということで。
It's 50. As in 0.50.
じゃあ続いてはおかゆんですが、どうですか？
Next up is Okayu, how are you feeling?
いけますか？自信あり？
Can you do it? Confident?
頑張りまゆ！頑張りまゆ！
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
じゃあ おかゆんのビビッタリ、スタート！
Okay, Okayu's 'Bibittari', start!
おかゆも練習があります。練習あるの優しいね。
Okayu also gets practice. It's kind of them to include practice.
よし！グラスを滑らせろ！いけるか？
Alright! Slide the glass! Can I do it?
へ？へ？へ？
Huh? Huh? Huh?
あれ？自分の注文じゃねーか それって。
Wait? Isn't that just your own order?
やばい、本番になっちゃった！
Oh no, it's time for the real thing!
本番だよ！頑張れ！
It's the real deal! Good luck!
待って、何！？
Wait, what!?
あ、それ、そんなお尻フリフリで...
Ah, with that butt shaking...
そんな勝てないんだからね！
You won't win like that!
ほら！
Look!
これで勝てませんかね？
Can't we win with this?
今の。
Just now.
なまけ！
Lazy!
なまけだろ！
You were being lazy!
なまけてたろ！
You were slacking off!
澪ちゃん強かった。
Mio-chan was strong.
難しそうだね、これね。
This looks difficult, doesn't it?
やーねー、うそ。
Yeah, really. No way.
ということで、皆さん。
And so, everyone.
こちら突然ではございますが、お知らせでございます。
This is sudden, but we have an announcement.
なんと無料配信をご覧の皆様はここまでとなります！
Actually, for those watching the free broadcast, it ends here!
引き続きをご覧になりたい方は、
If you want to continue watching,
ぜひ ABEMA PPV にてチケットの購入、お願いします！
please purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV!
お願いします！
Please do!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
あっさりバイバイだな。
That was a quick goodbye.
ね、これからもね、あのめちゃめちゃ楽しいゲーム、
Right, from now on, with super fun games,
ゲストもいるのでね。
and guests too.
楽しんでいただけますよう、よろしくお願いします。
We hope you enjoy it, thank you.
お願いします。
Please.
それでは。
Well then.
見に来てね！
Come watch!
またね！
See you!
またねー！
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full show is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Check the QR code for streaming details!
豪華購入特典: オリジナルボイスドラマと限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像がもらえる！
Deluxe Purchase Bonuses: Get an original voice drama and live photos with limited handwritten messages!
G-A-M-E-S
Let's go!
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
G-A-M-E-S
Are you ready? Go!
Up next
Wait!
G-A-M-E-S
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!
豪華購入特典：オリジナルボイスドラマと限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像もらえる！
Luxury Purchase Bonus: Get an original voice drama and a live image with a limited handwritten message!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
I'm ready!
にゃん！
Meow!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
Alright!
超超超超ゲーマーズ！
Cho Cho Cho Cho Gamers!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!